http://www.assda.asn.au/component/content/article/13-about-assda-pages/97-privacy-statement

HomeAbout ASSDAAbout ASSDAAchievements and MilestonesBoard of DirectorsOur SponsorsOur MembersBecome a MemberLevels of MembershipMember TestimonialsAssociate Membership ProgramOffering and BenefitsOur Associate MembersApply to JoinStainless SteelWhat is Stainless Steel?Benefits of Stainless SteelTypes of Stainless SteelAusteniticDuplexFerriticMartensiticPrecipitation HarderningSustainabilityPublicationsPublicationsAustralian Stainless Reference ManualAustralian Stainless MagazineStainless Steel Stock GuideASSDA Food Code of PracticeBlue Book: Code of PracticeTechnical InfoTechnical InfoProperties of Stainless SteelsGrade Selection200 Series Stainless Steels: CrMn Grades304: The Place to Start316: The First Step UpGrade 2205 for High Corrosion Resistance and StrengthQuestions of CarbonStainless Steel vs. Galvanised SteelSurface Finishes2B, 2D and BA Cold Rolled FinishesPickling and PassivationNo 4: The Workhorse FinishMirror, Profiles and Coloured SurfacesMill FormsMechanical TreatmentFabrication and Special Finishing MethodsCrevices and CorrosionChemical Surface TreatmentsStainless Fabrication: Common Traps to AvoidEnvironment, Health and SafetyBody PiercingLife-Cycle CostingRecyclingUsing Acids With Stainless SteelWeldingTechnical FAQsFAQ 1: Galvanic/Dissimilar Metal CorrosionFAQ 2: Cleaning Your Indoor Stainless SteelFAQ 3: Magnetic Effects of Stainless SteelsFAQ 4: Testing for Grade ConfirmationFAQ 5: Galling and its ControlFAQ 6: Preventing Coastal Corrosion (Tea Staining)FAQ 7: Guidelines for Use of Stainless Steel UndergroundFAQ 8: General Corrosion ResistanceFAQ 9: Welding Dissimilar MetalsFAQ 10: Thermal Expansion and Design of Stainless Steel FabricationsFAQ 11: Stainless Steel and Fire ResistanceFAQ 12: Coloured and Patterned Stainless SteelTechnical AlertsAirspace of Indoor PoolsHF Acid SchedulingStainless Steel Threaded FittingsApplicationsTransportTechnical InfoStainless Steel TrainingResidential and CommercialProcess and Heavy EngineeringMarineInfrastructureEnvironmentArchitectural Building ProductsArt and DesignQuick LinksStainless Steel Industry LinksTrainingTrainingStainless Steel Specialist CourseEngineering/Architectural SeminarsStainless Steels for Lecturers and Students of Architecture and Civil EngineeringNews & EventsASSDA Accredited FabricatorsASSDA Accreditation SchemeASSDA Accredited FabricatorsCode of Ethics and PracticeBenefitsAchieving ASSDA AccreditationStainless Steel Specialists RegisterArchitecturalFood, Dairy and BeverageHeavy IndustrialLight CommercialTechnical Inquiry
Privacy Statement
1. About this Privacy StatementThe Australian Stainless Steel Development Association (ASSDA) is bound by the National Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act 1998 (Commonwealth) in relation to the handling of personal information. This statement sets out its commitment to privacy.
2. Personal information collectedASSDA recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information collected for members and others seeking technical assistance from ASSDA. The nature of personal information collected and maintained by ASSDA generally comprises name, address, contact details (including phone, fax and email), web address and member business category. In addition to the above, personal information may be sought from members and third parties seeking technical advice or assistance from ASSDA including information pertaining to the nature of the technical issue arising and the assistance sought. Basic contact details are also sought from persons who attend ASSDA's seminars, courses and conferences. Personal information is collected for the purposes of establishing and building a database of businesses engaged in the use or fabrication of stainless steel products in Australia consistent with the objects for which ASSDA was incorporated.
3. Use and disclosure of personal informationUnless you have instructed us not to do so personal information may be used for:
(a) Preparation of member registry details which are included on the ASSDA website and in certain ASSDA publications for the purpose of promoting the use of stainless steel in Australia and the services of members of ASSDA;
(b) The purpose of publishing in ASSDA publications technical data and anecdotal information of interest to the stainless steel industry. Permission of the member or third party providing the technical data or anecdotal information will be sought prior to any such publication;
(c) Publishing a profile on a particular member or industry group. Again, before any use is made of personal information for this purpose the consent of the member or group will be obtained before publication.
ASSDA will not sell, rent or trade personal information.
4. Personal information qualityASSDA's goal is to ensure that personal information is accurate, complete and up to date. To assist with this, please contact ASSDA if any of the details you have provided change. Further, if you believe the information ASSDA has about you is not accurate, complete or up to date contact us and we will use all reasonable efforts to correct the information.
5. Access to personal informationYou are entitled under the Privacy Act to access the information ASSDA holds about you. ASSDA wishes to make this as simple as possible. Any such request should be addressed to the Privacy Officer, ASSDA by letter, facsimile or email. ASSDA requests that you be reasonably specific about the information you require to avoid unnecessary delays. Where you establish that the personal information that ASSDA holds about you is not accurate, complete or up to date ASSDA will correct its records as necessary. You may be charged an administration fee for providing access in accordance with your request. Your request will usually receive a response within 30 days.
6. SecurityASSDA protects the personal information it collects by maintaining appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. ASSDA requires third parties that process personal information on its behalf to follow stringent standards of security and confidentiality and towards that end, whenever ASSDA engages other organisations to provide support services, it requires them to conform to its privacy standards and to allow ASSDA to audit them for compliance.
7. ComplaintsIf you have reason to believe that ASSDA has breached the National Privacy Policies outlined in this document, you are urged to raise this with the ASSDA Privacy Officer. To make this easier you can obtain a form on request from ASSDA for you to describe and send in your concern. ASSDA will investigate all complaints and respond within fourteen (14) days. If it finds a complaint justified it will promptly resolve it. If necessary, ASSDA will change policies and procedures to maintain appropriate standards.
8. Website(a) When you visit the ASSDA website, our service provider makes a record of your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:
The type of browser and operating system you are using
The address of the referring site (i.e. the previous site that you visited)
Your server's IP address (a number unique to the computer through which you are connected to the internet)
The date and time of your visit
The address of pages accessed and the documents downloaded
No attempt will be made to otherwise identify users or their browsing activity except, in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider's logs.
(b) The ASSDA website contains links to other sites. ASSDA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the contents of such linked websites. These links are for the users' convenience only and do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by ASSDA of the content, policies or practices of those third party sites.
Prev
Next
Australian Stainless Steel Development Association (ASSDA)Level 9, 307 Queen Street, Brisbane QLD 4000 Australia+61 7 3220 0722  \  assda@assda.asn.au
What is stainless steel?
